http://4medicalwear.com/privacy.html

Try Before You Buy
MDF Stethoscopes, Cuffs, Aneroids.
Contact
Have a Question?
Your short message goes here.
Name *
Email *
Message *
Shopping Cart - count_contents();?> item(s) - format($_SESSION['cart']->show_total());?>
Try Before You Buy
MDF Stethoscopes, Cuffs, Aneroids.
Categories
Fashion SealDress PantsPolo ShirtsKnit ShirtsWoven ShirtsFood and BeverageHousekeepingPantsTry Before You BuyMDF Stethoscopes, Cuffs, Aneroids.WorkwearSpecials ...New Products ...Featured Products ...All Products ...
What's New  [more]
Reviews  [more]
There are currently no product reviews.
Featured  [more]
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY
Thank you for visiting the Scrubs division of the Medical Wear website.
Protecting consumer privacy is very important to us. Our Online Privacy
Statement is available to inform you about our collection and use of
personal information so that you can make informed choices about how
your own information is collected and used. This Online Privacy
Statement reflects the Medical Wear policies covering personal
information collected at this website on or after the effective date
shown above.
We believe that information used responsibly benefits consumers and the
economy, whether it is information we house on behalf of consumers
conducting transactions or information we collect on behalf of our
business clients. For example, we use consumer information every day to
ensure fast and accurate processing of hundreds of thousands of money
transfers. In addition, Medical Wear strives to better serve our
customers by offering goods and services that we believe fit their
needs and interests. When identifying an opportunity, Medical Wear may
use consumer information it has collected in an effort to identify
consumers who may be interested in that opportunity. For more than few
years, consumers and businesses have relied on Medical Wear for safe
and reliable service. The relationships we have developed through the
years have been established based on mutual trust. Each day we and
employees and agents strive to reinforce our commitment to our clients
and consumers. Central to that commitment is ensuring that we abide by
a set of privacy policies, which are outlined below. These policies
guide us in the collection and use of information as well as employee
responsibilities in protecting your privacy. We use personal
information about consumers only in a manner consistent with these
policies.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
Medical Wear collects personal information in order to offer or provide
goods and services to consumers and our customers. We may obtain this
information from a variety of sources:
· Directly from customer applications, questionnaires and other materials submitted to us by customers;
· From transactions in which Medical Wear and consumers are involved;
· From clickthru activity on our web sites; and
· From a variety of third-party sources, such as our business
customers, government repositories, consumer reporting agencies and
other financial institutions.
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
Medical Wear does not disclose customer information to third parties
without first giving customers an opportunity to opt-out of certain
kinds of disclosures. There are some disclosures to third parties that
are not subject to the opt-out, such as disclosures necessary to
effect, administer or enforce a transaction requested by you, to
companies that perform services for us or to prevent fraud.
Finally, Medical Wear may disclose information about former customers
to third parties and companies with which Medical Wear is affiliated,
as well as unaffiliated third parties. Those disclosures may consist of
the following:
· Financial background information describing a customer's financial status;
· Identification information, such as name and address data;
· Transaction information, such as account activity, debit activity or credit activity; and
· Other information relating to financial matters.
RECIPIENTS OF INFORMATION
Medical Wear may disclose consumer information to companies affiliated
with Medical Wear and to companies or other parties not affiliated with
Medical Wear
(subject to consumers' opt-out rights)
These recipients include:
· Financial institutions, such as banks, credit card companies and brokerage houses;
· Companies that process transactions or provide other services for us;
· Government agencies; and
· In addition, under United States law Medical Wear is permitted to
disclose customer information to certain recipients, like credit
reporting.
WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROTECTING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF PERSONAL CONSUMER INFORMATION.
Medical Wear limits access to personal information to those employees
of Medical Wear and its affiliates who need it to fulfill their
business responsibilities.
Employees must adhere to Medical Wear privacy policies. Employees
violating these policies may be subject to disciplinary action, up to
and including dismissal.
Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our
contractual requirements to ensure that sensitive personal information
is safeguarded.
WE USE APPROPRIATE SECURITY SAFEGUARDS.
At Medical Wear, security is a priority. We employ appropriate measures
to protect consumer information against unauthorized access,
disclosure, alteration or destruction. These may include, among others,
encryption, physical access security and other appropriate
technologies. Medical Wear continually reviews and enhances its
security systems, as necessary.
WE MAINTAIN PROCEDURES TO ASSURE THE QUALITY OF INFORMATION WE
COLLECT AND WHERE APPLICABLE, WE WILL INFORM CONSUMERS ABOUT HOW THEY
CAN ACCESS THEIR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND MAKE CORRECTIONS, IF
NECESSARY.
Medical Wear employs appropriate measures to assure the quality of
information we collect directly from consumers. Where Medical Wear
collects information directly from consumers or sources other than our
business customers, we permit them, if possible, to dispute or correct
any erroneous or out-of-date personally identifiable information. Of
course, this correction would not be possible if the information is
proprietary to one of our business customers, reflects historical
transaction information or if correction would violate the privacy or
legal rights of a third party. Where applicable, we abide by laws
related to such information. You can correct factual errors in your
personally identifiable information by sending us a written request
that credibly shows error. We reserve the right to independently verify
claims made. To protect your privacy and security, we also will take
reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. We
reserve the right to assess a service charge for providing you any
information in connection with your request.
THE Medical Wear WEBSITE IS NOT DIRECTED AT CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13.
Our website is not directed at children under the age of 13 and Medical
Wear does not collect or maintain information at our website from those
we actually know are under the age of 13.
WEBSITE MAY BE LINKED TO OTHER WEBSITES
Medical Wear may create links to third party websites. Medical Wear is
not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by
websites that are linked from our website.
OPT OUT RIGHT
Medical Wear may disclose consumer information to third parties as
described earlier in this notice. Many of these disclosures are
beneficial to consumers because they permit goods and services of
interest to consumers to be offered to consumers at attractive rates.
We strive to give consumers choices about how their data will be used.
You have the right to opt-out of (direct us not to make) these
disclosures when the consumer information is about you. Of course,
there are some disclosures to third parties that are not subject to the
opt-out, such as disclosures necessary to effect, administer or enforce
a transaction requested by you, to companies that perform services for
us or to prevent fraud. When you use this service, you will be asked
whether you wish to opt out. If you wish to opt out, simply check the
appropriate box and submit your choice.
If you have any questions or indeed comments about our Online Privacy
Statement,or for some reason believe we have not adhered to our
statement, please contact:
E-mail the Medical Wear Data Protection Officer: medwear2003@yahoo.com
We may alter this statement as needed for certain products and services
and to abide by local laws or regulations around the world. Medical
Wear reserves the right to amend or modify this statement from time to
time. We urge you to review this statement whenever you visit in order
to obtain the most current statement. You may change your choices at
any time.
Back
Customer ServiceCustomer ServiceContact UsShipping & ReturnsAbout UsPrivacy NoticeConditions of Use
Copyright © 2020 4Medicalwear's Fashion Seal Scrub Store.
Powered by 4medicalwear.com. has the complete range of Fashion Seal uniforms.
